koalalist.com 2016-12-10

# Privacy Policy | Aldaniti Network

## Privacy Statement

Aldaniti International Network Limited (‘Aldaniti’) is the proprietor of the site http://www.aldaniti.net and responsible for all the sweepstakes promoted by Aldaniti. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy statement, you should first contact us using the contact details at Contact Information. Aldaniti recognizes that your privacy and the protection of your personal information is important to you. This privacy statement discloses how Aldaniti helps to protect your personal information while using the Aldaniti web site http://www.aldaniti.net or the sweepstakes promoted by Aldaniti.

Aldaniti is registered under the Data Protection Act 1998 under registration number Z1688527. The personal information that you provide to Aldaniti is covered by the safeguards set out in that Act. To find out more information about the Act please visit http://www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk.

This privacy statement, operation of the site http://www.aldaniti.net and each of the sweepstakes promoted by Aldaniti are regulated by English law.

**Collection of your personal information:**  
In order to use this site, you must first register with Aldaniti by completing the registration form. You will be asked to confirm your acceptance of the following statement before you can start the registration process:

“This present sweepstake/competition is carried out with the objective to incorporate your personal information in the marketing database, property of Aldaniti International Network, Ltd. Should you not wish that your personal information forms part of this mentioned database, we kindly ask you not to participate in this competition/sweepstake. Furthermore, if you do not inform us otherwise, your participation in this sweepstake is automatically treated as your permission to include your personal information in our database. Should you object to your personal information forming part of these databases mentioned above, please click here.”

You also agree to the terms and conditions of the privacy statement that govern how your information will be processed.”

Please note that you may withdraw any consent that you have given in connection with this site by logging on and amending your details at the site.

During registration you will also be asked to give contact information (such as name, surname, postal address, telephone and email address) and some demographic information (such as age and gender). Once you have registered you will automatically receive a welcome email, and a newsletter packed with great prizes for you to win or offers that may be of interest to you.

You will have additional options at different points in the site to provide more information about yourself (such as details of the mobile network that you use, number of children that you have or car owned by you). We encourage you to take advantage of these options, so we can provide you with a more personalized experience on our site.

Use of your personal information:  
Aldaniti will not use or share your personal information in a manner that differs from what is described within this Privacy Statement or the registration opt-in statement without your prior written consent.

**General disclosure of personal information**

The information that you provide will be used:

  1. by Aldaniti and carefully selected third parties to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by post or telephone where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.;

  2. by carefully selected third parties to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and they may contact you by post, telephone or electronic means (e-mail or SMS) only if you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.

  3. by Aldaniti to determine the order of the questionnaires and prizes that are displayed to you at the site.

  4. by Aldaniti to provide you (provided you are an existing customer) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous transaction with you and we may contact you by post, telephone or by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) for such purposes.

  5. by Aldaniti to allow you to participate in interactive features of the site, when you choose to do so.

  6. by Aldaniti to notify you about changes to the site.

  7. by Aldaniti to carry out its obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and Aldaniti.

If you do not want Aldaniti to use your data in this way, or to pass your details on to third parties for marketing purposes, please tick the relevant box situated on the registration form.

**Sponsored sweepstakes and Co-branded sites:**

The site hosts a number of questionnaires. By completing a questionnaire and consenting to be contacted by Aldaniti or a third party, you consent to Aldaniti and the third party sending you information about products and/or services of interest to you based on the answers that you gave in completing the questionnaire and where you have consented to receive such information. The information that you provide may in addition be used, by Aldaniti and carefully selected third parties to provide you with information and offers by email, sms, voice, post or other appropriate means of communications about products and/or services that may be of interest to you where you have consented to receive such information. If you would prefer not to receive such information or offers please indicate your preference by ticking the box provided, located on the “Amend Details” page and/or the questionnaire.

**Managing your personal information:**

The data you provide to Aldaniti will be held as you have provided it. You may at any time amend or update your data by sending us an E-mail with your updated information to info@aldaniti.net.

You are entitled to see the information held about you and you may ask us to make any necessary changes to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date. If you wish to do this, please contact us. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.

**Deregistration and un-subscribing from our database:**

You may at any time deregister from Aldaniti by contacting us by sending us an E-mail to info@aldaniti.net. You may also decline to receive any further E-mails that Aldaniti or carefully selected third parties send out by contacting Aldaniti at the address above.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by emailing us or in writing sent to Aldaniti International Network, 12 Brookend Street Ross-on-Wye, HerefordShire HR9 7EG, United Kingdom.

**Security and storage of your personal information:**

Any data that you provide that is retained by Aldaniti will be held in Aldaniti’s central database, to be accessed by reference to interest or demographic categories in order to provide you with information about those interests you have selected. The process of supplying you with this information is at all times under Aldaniti’s control although specialist third party suppliers who may be sub-contracted to assist in the process. Such third parties will hold your personal data and it may also be transferred, stored, and processed by them or a sub-processor on their behalf at a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) . Both parties will only process your data in accordance with our instructions and for no other purposes but they may contact you post or telephone for the purposes of informing you of similar goods or services to which you may have already transacted for via Aldaniti or where you have expressly stated that you would like to be contacted on the registration form. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing and processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your personal data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

The Internet is not a 100% secure medium for communication and, accordingly, Aldaniti cannot guarantee the security of any information you send to Aldaniti via the Internet. Aldaniti is not responsible for any loss or damage you or others may suffer as a result of the loss of confidentiality of such information.

**Use of Cookies:**

Aldaniti uses Sitestat, a Nedstat product, to measure and analyse information with respect to your visits to the Aldanitisite. To that effect we use your IP address to collect, among other things, internet traffic data and data regarding your browser type and computer.

Aldaniti also uses cookies to improve your login experience. A cookie is a small file that is stored on your computer when you visit a website. If you visit the website again, it is recognized as a repeat visit by means of the cookie. The cookie contains merely a unique number and therefore no personal data, and the cookie cannot be used to identify you when you visit any other web sites including web sites of third parties such as Nedstat. Aldaniti also separately uses session cookies to store data on our server that are individually identifiable. When you log out of the site, these session cookies are deleted from your computer.

In addition Aldaniti permits carefully selected third parties to:

  1. use cookies at the Aldaniti site. Aldaniti has no access to or control over these cookies;

  2. employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the full stop at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. Other websites that you visit may store their own cookies on your computer. Aldaniti recommends that you read each site’s privacy statement to understand their policies and practices regarding the use of cookies.

You have the ability to accept or decline any of the cookies located at the Aldaniti site whether or not the cookies are provided by Aldaniti or a carefully selected third party using the settings on your browser. If you have cookies disabled in your browser you are still able to use the Aldaniti site but you will not have the benefit of an automatic login.

The functionality of the Aldaniti site depends upon your browser accepting session cookies. Aldaniti tracks visitors to and on the Aldaniti site by using referrer tracking. Aldaniti uses click thru and open mail tracking when sending emails. This process allows Aldaniti and carefully selected third parties the ability to profile the recipients of their communications.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement:**

Aldaniti may update this Privacy Statement from time to time. Aldaniti will also obtain your opt-in consent for any updates to this Privacy Statement that materially expand the sharing or use of your personal information in ways not disclosed in this Privacy Statement at the time of collection.

**Limits on Aldaniti’s liability**

The information and functionality contained on the Aldaniti site is provided “as is” and no warranty (express or implied) is given. Aldaniti does not warrant that the information and functionality is accurate, suitable, fit for purpose, free from defects or viruses (or other harmful components), adequate, timely or complete. Nothing on the Aldaniti site shall constitute an offer to sell or solicitation or offer to buy any investment, security or financial instrument or any advice or recommendation in respect of any investment, security or financial instrument or engage in any transaction or otherwise constitute advice of any kind. The Aldaniti site may provide hypertext links to other sites created by other organisations from time to time. Because those other sites are not under our control, we cannot guarantee the quality, accuracy or performance of those sites nor is our connection to those sites an endorsement or adoption of the views expressed or of the products and services sold or advertised on or the information available at those sites. Please note that under no circumstances will Aldaniti be held responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any loss or damage that is caused or alleged to have been caused to you in connection with your use of, or reliance on, any content, goods or services available on any of those other sites.

You may not provide a hypertext link from your site to any of the Websites without our prior written permission. Please contact Aldaniti if you wish to request such permission using the contact details given above.

Your use of the Aldaniti site is subject to you using the Aldaniti site in a responsible manner and in accordance with any guidelines, operating manuals, standards and requirements issued or brought to your attention by Aldaniti from time to time. You should inform info@aldaniti.net immediately if you discover any act or omission by any person which is, or which if done by you or on your behalf would be, contrary to any of these terms and conditions. Without limiting this requirement, you must not:

(a) post or transmit any information that is threatening, defamatory, obscene, indecent, seditious, offensive, pornographic, abusive, liable to incite racial hatred, discriminatory, menacing, scandalous, inflammatory, blasphemous, in breach of confidence, in breach of privacy or which may cause annoyance or inconvenience; or

(b) post or transmit any information or software for which you have not obtained all necessary licences and/or approvals; or

(c) post or transmit any information that constitutes or encourages conduct that would be considered a criminal offence, gives rise to civil liability, or otherwise be contrary to any national or international law or infringe the rights of any third party; or

(d) post or transmit any information or software that is technically harmful (including, without limitation, computer viruses, logic bombs, Trojan horses, worms, harmful components, corrupted data or other malicious software or harmful data); or

(e) interfere with the proper operation of the Aldaniti site or prevent any other user from using the Aldaniti site; or

(f) post, transmit, publish, reproduce, distribute or exploit any information or software for commercial purposes; or

(g) reproduce or knowingly permit the reproduction of any technologies (including software) or documentation supplied or made available to you by Aldaniti in connection with the Aldaniti site; or

(h) modify, merge, translate, adapt, reproduce, decompile, reverse engineer, make any derivative works or attempt to circumvent any security feature in respect of any technologies (including software) or documentation supplied or made available to you by Aldaniti in connection with the Aldaniti site; or

(i) undertake any act or omission in respect of the technologies, documentation or information located at or available to you by means of the Aldaniti site that is not permitted by these terms and conditions and which, absent permission, is exclusively reserved by operation of law to the owner of them or of the intellectual property rights in them; or

(j) other than by means of a hypertext link as permitted by us in writing, distribute or make available the Aldaniti site or their contents over any medium; other than to the extent permitted in law.

Aldaniti will cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing Aldaniti to disclose the identity or locate anyone acting in contravention of these terms and conditions.

It is the responsibility of each person accessing or using the Aldaniti site to evaluate the accuracy, completeness, reliability and usefulness of any information or material available at the Aldaniti site. All warranties, conditions or other terms implied by statute, common law or otherwise are excluded to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law. Aldaniti does not give any assurance that the Aldaniti site will be error free or available for use and Aldaniti hereby excludes to the fullest extent possible in law all liability and responsibility for any amount or kind of loss, damage, expenses, costs or liability that may result to you or a third party including without limitation, any direct, indirect, punitive or consequential loss or damage, or any loss of income, profits, anticipated savings, additional operational or administrative costs or expenses, goodwill, data, contracts, use of money whether in tort (including without limitation, negligence), contract, operation of law or otherwise in connection with the use, inability to use, or the results of use of the Aldaniti site, any sites linked to the Aldaniti site or the information on the Aldaniti site or act, omission or conduct of any person using or relying on the Aldaniti site. If any of these terms and conditions would otherwise be held invalid, the invalid term or condition shall be interpreted as applicable only to the extent permitted without being invalid and the remainder of the terms and conditions shall not be affected.

You acknowledge that the provisions of this disclaimer are fundamental to the terms and conditions without which Aldaniti would not make the Aldaniti site available to you. You acknowledge that the limitations and exclusions in these terms and conditions are reasonable in all the circumstances.

**Contact information**

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact Aldaniti International Network, Ltd by Email: info@aldaniti.net

In writing, please send to:

Aldaniti International Network,

12 Brookend Street Ross-on-Wye,

HerefordShire

HR97EG,

United Kingdom
